

# **IMOGEN DREWS**

## **PROFILE**

I am a frontend developer currently pursuing a master's in Creative Technologies at the Film University Babelsberg Konrad Wolf. After earning my bachelor's degree in film in Johannesburg, I moved to Germany, where I completed a Full Stack Web Development course. With over three years of experience as a frontend developer, I decided to merge my creative background in film with technology, exploring new ways to bridge storytelling and innovation.

- 0151 127 31191
- @ imoleadrews@gmail.com
- Am Diebsteich 1, 22761, Hamburg
- in LinkedIn
- Duel German and South African citizenship

# **EDUCATION**

CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIES
MASTERS
10/2024 - present

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER COURSE 08/2020 - 12/2020

FILM AND TELEVISION DEGREE 01/2014-12/2017

# Film university Babelsberg Konrad Wolf, Potsdam

Currently completing a masters in Creative Technologies

## **WBS Coding School, Berlin**

 Received a certificate for completing an intensive, full-time full stack coding training course

# University of the Witwatersrand, Johannesburg

• Fundamentals of Post Production and Cinematography

# **EXPERIENCE**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER 03 / 2021 - 10/2024

# Polymetis GmbH, Hamburg

· Created third-party apps for the Atlassian Marketplace

RESEARCH INTERN 08/2017 - 11/2017

## **Fort Productions Offices, Johannesburg**

- Researched information for upcoming productions
- Developed skills of meeting the demands of clients

# **PRESENTATIONS**

Atlas Camp 2023

#### How we built it: AI, Privacy & GPUs in the browser

In this presentation, we explained how we went about creating our latest machine-learning app Erica. A link to this presentation can be found <u>here</u>.